From when I was little
I had a question in my mind.
I heard that "I think therefore I am"
are the words of an ancient philosopher.
But I didn't think.
I thought about someone else.
That perhaps the person over there
is myself as well...
Episode 1
"I think about others"
"Think about others."
When I did that I had turned into someone else.
But no more than five seconds.
After that I immediately returned to my own self.
Furthermore for the duration
my body completely loses consciousness.
Often I would find myself
injured in some way.
Furthermore I can only possess someone
that is within my line of sight.
So I couldn't use it for lewd things.
At most it was for possessing someone
that angry me off
only to pick a fight with a stranger
then return to myself.
That kind of retaliation was
all I could use this for.
You! What do you
think you just did huh?
But finally I came up with an idea
that can take full advantage of this special ability.
Five minutes before time.
I could possess one smart guy in class
after another memorize the answers
memorize the answers and fill in my answers
after returning... and I repeat that.
Year-End Test Standings
1 - Yu Otosaka
Of course I'm planning on attending
a very prestigious high school.
However unlike a normal test I don't know
who is intelligent during an entrance exam...
Ever since I've snuck into
prestigious cram schools one after another
pretending to be a student
of that cram school.
Which student facing entrance exams
apply to which schools?
And which subjects were they best at?
I researched all of that very thoroughly.
High School
Entrance Exam Venue
And so I found one student after another that
was vying to enter the same school as I was.
And successfully got admitted
to an elite high school.
Entrance Ceremony
Now a word from the representative
for the new students.
Yu Otosaka please go ahead.
Yes!
So that means he's the top of the class!
And he's good-looking to boot...!
Entrance Ceremony
Today for us new students you have organized
a grand ceremony of this sort
and we are deeply in gratitude for it.
Wrapped in the warm rays
of the spring sunshine
we are now able to be a part
of the well-established ranks of Hinomori High School.
Hey hey....
Isn't he attractive?
Yeah he might be your type Mitchon.
Huh? What? Yumi doesn't seem
to be against the idea either?
We are very grateful for
this opportunity today.
Previous Term Class Ranking
1 - Yu Otosaka
Sorry for the sudden email:
My name is Sugimoto from Class 1-2.
Will you possibly come to the back
of the school building after school?
I will be waiting for you till the night.
This again...
Stuff like this is happening more often.
Not only am I superior
as the top of the class academically
I'm one of the more physically attractive.
It's impossible to not be
popular among girls like this.
Sheesh I'll hurry them all on home.
I'm sorry for calling you
over all the way out here!
That's fine. What did you want from me?
Um I'm fine from starting as just friends...
But can you think about dating me please?
Well... In order to keep my grades up
at where they are now
I have to shave time to
sleep to keep studying.
I don't have the luxury
of dealing with other people. So I'm sorry.
Of course that's a pack of lies.
I don't study whatsoever.
I see I understand.
I'm sorry for calling you out like this so suddenly!
There's no way I would choose
normal girls like you ilk.
The one I'm after...
So Yumi you missed
the special program from yesterday?!
Of course is the madonna of this school...
Yumi Shirayanagi.
I will...
...make you mine!
I know I will definitely get a chance.
It all lies in how I use the five seconds
which are the limits of my ability!
And so I was texting until 3 o'clock last night
so I overslept... it was so hard for me to get up!
That's it!
So...
Mitchon what's wrong?
Call the police!
Are you all right?
Oh it looks like he's okay.
I'm so glad...
That was close but that
went according to plan...
Yumi!
Are you all right?
That was a close one.
Yumi you were about to be run over by a truck
when Otosaka from class 1 saved you!
Is that true...?
Yeah. Are you hurt anywhere?
Let's go to the nurse's office. Can you walk?
Yes...
Then I'll go home now.
Please wait!
U-Um...
The two of us were about to go eat
our favorite pancakes together...
would you like to come with us?
I'll have to pass.
It's better to keep that among friends right?
But you just saved my life!
I'd like to properly repay that
and I'd like to chat with you a little while longer...
Whoa I have a call. Who is it?
Then I'll go home. Yup yup yup.
Mitchon what's wrong?
My big brother suddenly came back from Kyoto
and he apparently ordered
top-end sushi for the entire family!
So I'm leaving the rest
to the two of you! Thanks!
That was an obvious farce
but a nice assist nonetheless Mitchon!
Sorry to make you wait.
Um there's a special way to eat this.
Oh?
Please mimic me.
If you do this the syrup
gets across to the entire thing.
Then stack them up cut
them and try a bite of it.
Amazing! Just by changing how you eat it
it gets this delicious? I never knew!
No matter how many times I
eat this it's delicious...
Oh um...
The song they're playing right now
is Haro-haro isn't it?
Haro-haro?
You don't know of them?
I had thought every boy knew of them very well.
So something like them is popular nowadays?
Otosaka can we go home
together from school
or have an occasional meal together
like this again sometime?
Sure I guess.
I'm so glad...
Shall we go home together today as well?
I will be waiting for you near the main gate.
Oh I shouldn't do this out loud.
I guess I'll hurry on over.
Yu Otosaka from class 1-1 please report immediately
to the student council room. I repeat...
What's this?
Yu Otosaka from class 1-1 please report immediately
to the student council room.
-Sorry I will be late.
-I will be waiting.
I'm Omura the student council president.
What do you want with me? I'm making someone
wait so I'd like you to make it quick.
That is really up to you. This is a copy of your
answer sheet to the aptitude test from the other day.
A perfect score... so marvelous.
The same exact test has
been placed right there.
Right here right now please try
to get a perfect score once again.
Huh?
What meaning is there behind that?
There is an accusation
that you may have cheated on the exam.
If you can get 90% or above you are innocent.
You will be deemed guilty if your score is any lower.
This is absurd! I will
excuse myself right now!
Concerning this case we have the authorization
of both the principal and the vice-principal.
If you escape now you will apparently
be expelled from the school.
E-Expelled?!
Now please begin.
Right there lies all of the answers...
I'll possess him and find out!
That's the only way!
Making such a fool of me!
What in the world has happened?
To me it only seemed like
you were tearing that up?
Got him!
Hello there I'm Tomori the student
council president... of another school though.
So I was recording you for all this time.
Can you take a look at the
video I just recorded?
Please take a note of the time.
You were not looking at him
the moment he ripped the answer sheet.
Yet you said he ripped it up.
Isn't that a bit strange?
I'll show you others.
You have a special ability
to possess other people.
Using that you cheat on every exam.
Isn't that right?
T-That's not true!
It's a sleeping disease!
I suddenly get tremendously sleepy
and can't fight that urge!
You really are a troublesome one.
I'll show you this now. Here.
A copy of your medical exams.
As far as this goes such
a disease doesn't exist.
Now please solve the problems on the test.
Such a farce! I can't deal with it!
I see... she had foreseen
that it would even end up this way.
Then everything from here on is my job.
Run! Right now!
!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes... I'm fine.
What?
What is going on here?!
You... what did you just do?
Teleportation.
Teleportation?
Yes. Just like it sounds I teleport instantly
to move to another location.
But this ability doesn't let me
conveniently stop exactly where I want.
Thanks to this ability I don't know
how many times I've been hospitalized...
What an incomplete ability!
But anyway what are you
going to do with me from now on?!
We will have you transfer over to our school.
Transfer?!
Yes. In this world there are many people
who possess special powers not just you.
However those special skills can be considered
an illness caught during adolescence
and will disappear in due time.
Until it goes away however please keep commuting
to our school the Hoshinoumi Academy.
Huh?!
I already have gotten permission from those
that have parental authority over you.
Such a story...
...exists.
However... you seem like you'd be popular
from just your looks.
Was there also a need to play the role of a genius
by cheating as much as possible?
That's the real question.
Oh but thanks to that
you were able to close the gap
between yourself and the female student
you were targeting.
Damn you!
What... she disappeared?
That is her ability.
It can't be... an ability
to become invisible?
No. To me it only looked
like her punching you.
Impossible... I was the only one
that couldn't see her?
Right. Her ability is to hide from
visual recognition from one target.
Every other human can see her as normal.
Another imperfect ability!
By the way you will enter
our student council as well.
Huh?
Your ability is useful
so I'd like you to cooperate with us.
For what?
To threaten those that abuse their powers
for no good just like you.
That is the kind of existence we are.
I'm home.
Welcome back Big Brother Yu!
Wait! Wow! What's wrong with your face?
Oh well um... it was an
incident during gym class...
Oh right there was
an amazing phone call from our uncle.
Ayu heard that she and Big Brother Yu
will transfer into Hoshinoumi Academy's
middle- and high-school
as scholarship students!
Is that really true?
Are you serious?
Well... it's true.
The house budget will benefit from this!
Furthermore the uncle is sending us
lots of tasty food to celebrate!
But that means
you have to transfer schools too.
That means you have to say goodbye
to your friends - is that all right?
Nowadays we can use smartphones to chat
while looking at each other's faces
so it's not going to be all that lonely.
Hoshinoumi Academy
Executive Office
I see...
Tonight's dinner is... ta-dah!
Congratulations!
Omelet rice your favorite
dish Big Brother Yu!
This again? I said time and again
that it was only when I was little...
Congrats! Now let's eat!
So sweet...
Using pizza sauce as the secret ingredient must
have been fitting for my tongue when I was a child.
How is it? Is it tasty?
Yeah it's tasty.
Really?
I want to eat Mom's omelet rice
for the first time in a while...
Mom huh? Who cares about someone like that.
Are you still upset?
Of course I am... She got divorced
and selfishly shoved custody over to our uncle.
Ayu doesn't understand too much of it
but would like to see you be forgiving!
We don't have any parents. Our only family
is you and me just the two of us.
I see... but Ayu sometimes thinks...
there was one more family member somewhere...
You and I are the only siblings. Do you see
someone in your dream or something?
You're right.
It's a weird feeling as
if it was really true.
It's totally a dream.
Hey we're going to be up early tomorrow
because we're moving right?
Why don't you get to sleep soon?
Please give me just a tiny
bit more of your time!
You really love stars don't you?
You can see way off into the distance
where people will never reach you know?
Ayu thinks that is an amazing thing!
You know if you keep talking only about
the stars at school you'll end up getting isolated.
Why is that?
Speaking from experience.
In living my life a foundation
is to liven up the conversation
by talking about what was on TV last night
instead of talk about the stars.
Experience? Foundation?
It's okay if you don't
understand. Go to sleep soon.
Roger that!
This is an amazingly huge room!
Can Ayu really use it all
alone with Big Brother Yu?
Yeah...
Thank you for your hard work!
I may not be much but allow me to help–
Hey the moving company guys
will do it so you don't have to.
I thought I could be at least
of some assistance however...
Don't take their jobs away from them.
Oh! Such a way of thinking
was something that Ayu didn't have!
Back at that time what had happened?
That's something I can't say...
Well... I'm going to transfer
to Hoshinoumi Academy now...
Well um... I'm sorry
for all the things that happened.
Until this ability goes away I can't be authorized
to travel to an area with no supervision...
Shirayanagi if you could
come see me instead I'd be delighted.
But that is just too far. At the least
can it be once a week and can we alternate?
Well... I'm sorry about that too.
I can't come here anymore on my own.
Why?
I can't say why...
I am forced to not mention anything
about this case to others.
There's nothing that I can do about it...
I am grateful for what you have done.
That feeling will never waver.
However I am not dating you yet.
So for me to chase you
in a one-sided manner is as if I was a stalker.
Of course I do feel bad about that.
However I can't go see you on my own.
I understand. From now on
let us walk our own separate paths.
That means...
I will never forget the feeling I have towards you
for saving my life as long as I live. That is all.
That can't be...
Thank you very much for saving me.
I really do appreciate it.
But this is where I bid you farewell.
I hope you stay well.
I got dumped... me...?
Hello! Excuse me! I've already let myself in!
What is it so suddenly?
It's tough when it's just the two of you right?
I came here to help.
Oh are all of you people
from the same school as Big Brother Yu?
Yes. We are from the student council.
I am Takajo and this is Tomori.
Since it's after school now
we thought we should help out a bit.
Unnecessary troubles.
Can we help you out?
Of course that would help us out a lot!
How cunning...!
Then we should split up and get things done.
Yes!
Please do!
This must be that delicious thing
that our uncle sent in congratulations
that Ayumi was talking about!
They're all Kin-san Ramen?!
I'll pretend I never saw this.
Ayumi can I show you a magic trick?
Oh... that's something I want to see!
Stay there. It will only be an instant.
Yup!
This is amazing!
This is more amazing than the people on TV!
Were you amused by that?
Yup yup yup!
Don't use your ability for play!
You've knocked Ayumi out of her wits!
If you're going to play
I'll have you go home!
Yeah yeah... your big brother is scary.
And you're helping us too!
Then we shall excuse ourselves here.
You're going to go home?
I'll make dinner so I'd like you to eat that at least...
We don't have enough dishes for four.
Or so he says.
It's all right. We'll meet again.
Yeah...
Oh Haro-haro.
So it is a fad after all.
That's right! Yusa Nishimori
known as Yusarin. She's so cute!
To think something like this sells...
that's the sign of the apocalypse.
Ayu's new school is right next to Big Brother Yu's!
So she wants to go to school together!
They'd think I have a
sis-com (sister complex).
Sis-com? Is that some kind of a contest?
It isn't.
But still Hoshinoumi Academy...
what a wonderful name!
Yeah it's a name that sounds like one
that was made just for you...
Hey.
That night I had a dream. I'm sure it was
because of Ayumi's farfetched announcement.
But who was that?