ATTIC CAT
CHAPTER 11
PRODUCED by Woon-hyun Jung
SCRIPT by Hyo-jung Min & Sun-kyung Koo
DIRECTED by Sa-hyun Kim
Kyung-min!
( hello? )
Jung-eun,
it's me.
I got curious about one thing.
what it's like..
'to like somebody'?
I mean,
how do you know
whether you like someone or not?
how?
you don't know about your mind?
maybe I don't.
I think,
I think
I haven't really liked somebody so far..
so I'm very confused now..
confused?
you like Hye-ryun, don't you?
uh?
yeah..
right, I like Hye-ryun.
that's right!
I like Hye-ryun!
now it's all clear!
thank you, bye!
ya!
what are you doing here?
you stayed there all night long?
you stayed up there?
I'm asking you,
you don't wanna talk to me?
what happened to you?
what is that?
you don't have to mind me anymore.
what?
I'm not interested in you.
I'm not interested in
whom you met & what you've done..etc.
so don't give me a shit any more.
ya..
your chief,
he looks like a nice guy.
ya,
it was not like that.
you got it wrong!
did I tell you something?
it's really not like that!
I said, I'm not interested
in what you've done.
I've been feeling guilty for you
for all the troubles I made, but now..
I'm free! I don't even feel guilty anymore!
good luck to you.
what?
and I'm giving you an advice as a friend,
don't be an 'easy' girl..
that's not good.
keep that in mind, okay?
you two went too far, huh?
that's not good..
I envy you, Jung-eun.
now your company's like..
buy 1 get 1 free for you!
you can get money, and your love there!
what a happy life for you, huh?
you gotta hurry!
he's waiting for you now!
he's waiting for you, right?
and give my regards to him.
oh, Jung-eun Nam!
good morning.
yeah..
uhm..
you didn't hit the button.
hello?
mom,
what's the matter?
the matter is..
the memorandum.
( give it back to me. )
I said, we don't need that kinda thing!
mom,
if you ever come again to see him
in his school,
I'll burn up the memorandum!
it's working hour now,
bye!
yes?
chief,
I finished my work today,
can I go home now?
if it's okay for you,
let's have dinner together.
you got an appointment tonight?
no, I'm free tonight.
let's have dinner together.
I got something to tell you.
okay, let's get out.
what do you like for dinner?
anything's fine.
you like lobsters?
yeah.
Jung-eun!
ya,
how come you're here?
I just dropped by.
who is he?
he's my chief.
chief, he's my brother.
how do you do?
my name is Jung-woo Nam.
where are you guys going now?
if it's alright for you,
let's have dinner together.
no, I'll take him to my home.
let's have dinner next time.
no, you don't have to.
I gotta have dinner.
let's go have dinner!
lobster for me, please.
same thing for me.
oh..
well..
do you come here often?
from time to time, yes.
I don't see much resemblance
between you two.
you don't?
everybody's saying that
we're the same shits!
is that right?
by the way,
how many siblings you have?
ya,
why are you asking such a question?
it's okay.
I have one younger sister.
I see..
then you're the only son to your parents.
yes..
are you living together with your parents?
my parents are living in u.s.,
and my sister's in france now,
she's studying there.
oh..
your family is very 'global'!
stop it..
do you mind..
if I ask you about your monthly income?
sorry for my brother bothering you.
it's alright.
see you again.
yes.
come see me again.
bye!
yeah, my brother Dong-june!
I'll call you, my brother!
bye my brother, Dong-june!
Dong-june, safe driving, okay?
Dong-june, I love ya!
his 'sedan' is..
shut up!
ya,
why are you doing this to me?
what are you talking bout?
you don't have to do this here!
yes, I have to do this.
I'm helping you..
don't you think so?
what are you doing here?
I'm taking some rest.
taking some rest?
that's good.
take your rest there forever!
Jung-eun, let's get inside.
man, it's so hot even in the night.
what did you have for dinner?
did he buy something expensive?
no, we just had 'lobsters'~
he's always buying lobsters.
hey,
don't make your bed here.
why not?
it's cool outside.
you sleep outside.
well,
there has been some misunderstanding between us.
yeah,
I admit that.
I admit that
you & my sister are just friends.
and there hasn't been nothing between you two.
yeah, I admit that.
so it's all in the past.
you don't ever come to
my sister's home again, okay?
how can you do this to me?
you're not my brother-in-law, right?
you are just a stranger to me!
har har har~
Jung-eun,
Jung-eun Nam!
Jung-eun!
what?
your brother..
wants me to get out.
you can get out then.
Jung-eun,
I'm getting outta here!
I'm really getting out!
don't call me back again!
wake up.
wake up!
what..
I said, wake up!
uh..good bye.
leave me alone..
I said, wake up!
why why why why!
don't raise your voice to me.
hey,
let me ask you one question.
when are you gonna get out of my sister's place?
what?
please have some manners.
you're living off my sister now, right?
so get outta this place ASAP.
what did you just say?
what a mean guy you are..
let's go.
ya,
what the hell is this?
you came?
as you can see, this is a tent.
where did you get this?
you bought this?
yeah, I bought it.
you can't get it for free.
where did you get the money for this?
I took 30,000 won from the kitchen..
and some more money from your drawer.
what?
you must be crazy!
that's our living expenses for this month!
I know, but..
you guys were behaving so mean.
so there's nothing I can do.
I need some place to sleep in.
what're ya doing?
ya ya!
stop reading the book.
peel garlic
until you make up the money for this tent.
no, I won't.
yes, you will!
no, I won't!
ya!
what?
put the garlic into basket.
no, I won't.
wanna see me getting mad?
no, I don't..
and I won't peel garlic, either.
ya!
what?
I'll make you bald
without a single piece of hair!
are you behaving like this
when you're with your chief?
what?
if he had seen you like this,
he'd just hate you!
oh, my hair..
Kyung-min,
go check the test result on the board.
oh I forgot,
is the result on the board?
- how about you? you checked your score?
- yeah,
by the way,
your answer sheets are on the board.
you buy me a drink!
my answer sheets on the board?
why?
( criminal law & bla bla bla.. )
who's got the highest score this time?
Kyung-min,
you got the highest score?
oh well,
it's not the real exam, you know.
it was just a trial test.
it's nothing!
what really matters is..
the real bar exam!
this test doesn't mean anything!
shut up.
my score is lower than I thought it to be..
bye!
granma,
I had my test score.
well,
I got the highest score
among present & past & future students!
party? oh no!
toda..
I can't come to your place today..
uh..see you next week, okay?
bye!
Jung-eun~
chief,
are you free tonight?
I got something to tell you.
I'm okay.
let's go.
your brother's not coming today?
no.
hello?
Jung-eun,
you're in your office?
now I'm at the lobby of..
how come you're here?
oh,
I was just passing by.
how are you?
how are you doing?
you finished your work today?
yeah, but..
I gotta have dinner with my chief.
if it's okay for you,
let's have dinner together.
Kyung-min, you go home first.
me & my chief have something to talk about.
we can have some talk next time.
let's go have dinner together.
no,
you guys can go without me.
'cause I'm a busy guy.
see you next time.
yeah.
see you later.
okay, have a good one.
excuse us.
are they going to have steaks?
I've got the highest score..
what do you wanna have for dinner?
you have something on your mind?
anything's fine for me.
what?
I'm gonna have a sam-gyop-sal(pork-belly)
party tonight.
join me or not, it's up to you!
can we really go?
yes.
so..
your brother's back home?
why did you do that to me?
what?
I think I should've slapped on your face.
but I was so stunned back then.
we were drunk at that time.
so I can forgive you about last time, but..
I don't want you to do that to me again.
well,
I like you..
so much.
what?
I told you that,
'how about me as your boyfriend?'
you remember?
that was not a joke.
oh,
I'm just..
you don't have to answer me right now.
think it over and..
answer me later.
Jung-eun..
I gotta go out after breakfast.
so peel all the garlic
before I come back, okay?
I'd rather get outta this place
than peel garlic!
do as you please.
yeah, I'll do as I please!
you want me to peel garlic?
I WON'T!
I told Kyung-min to come back home until today.
but he hasn't come back yet.
he'll come back with the memorandum.
he still hasn't got the memorandum back.
and he's still hanging around outside home..
oh, what's going on now?
don't worry.
he promised to get the memorandum back to us.
are they really 'just' friends?
what if they're living together as lovers?
oh..
she's way below
Kyung-min's own standard of girls.
just let them be.
Kyung-min has nothing to lose.
but she has something to lose.
Kyung-min stamped on it
because he has such a weak character!
that means he might do something worse!
Kyung-min, you're home?
oh, mother!
glad you came here.
what are you doing now?
- well,
- you are peeling garlic?
you're an exam student!
how come you aren't studying now?
you gave up the bar exam?
no, I didn't give it up.
garlic is for some extra bucks.
what is that tent?
oh..
I want some camping atmosphere.
that helps me to concentrate on my study.
study in the tent?
wake up, you're an exam student!
where's Jung-eun?
she's off to the bank.
oh yeah?
let's get inside & have some talk.
yeah.
oh..what are you doing?
I'm helping you packing up your things.
these are your things, right?
right, but..
mother, Jung-eun hasn't come back yet.
you can wait 'til she comes back.
you shouldn't call me 'mother'.
people will misunderstand it.
can you stop calling me 'mother'?
let's pack up.
you go first with this bag.
I'll send the rest of your things by the postal service.
oh mother,
I can't go.
you can't?
why not?
at least I have to say goodbye to Jung-eun.
goodbye?
you can say goodbye by phone!
- mother!
- go away!
mother!
I'm not prepared for leaving this place..
mom!
what are you doing here?
Jung-eun!
he wants to leave this place.
so I'm helping him out.
no! I'm not leaving here.
you get inside with your bag.
I'm okay here.
I said, get inside!
okay.
what the hell you're doing here, mom?
getting him out of this place.
getting him outta this place?
why?
what if your chief got to know about it?
he'll misunderstand it!
my chief?
mom, he's just my chief,
not my boyfriend!
I heard that you're going out with him.
and Kyung-min got angry about that.
you heard it from Jung-woo?
he's always making stories!
don't you know that?
anyway,
you shouldn't live with him.
you two are not gonna get married, right?
why are you still with him?
you should let him go.
no,
I can't let him go.
you can't?
why not?
why you can't let him go?
mom,
I can't live without him!
( what did you just say? )
I gotta go now.
don't peel garlic any more and..
concentrate on your study, understand?
you don't answer me?
yes, mother.
I'll study hard.
good bye. take care.
mom,
Jung-eun,
it's good to be back in my room.
it's not a good idea
to change the place where you sleep.
it's cool outside, but..
too many mosquitoes!
see this?
ya!
you're sleeping?
the tent is..
I don't think we can get the refund of it, so..
let's keep it until I pass the bar exam.
I'll take you to a vacation with it, okay?
and,
I'm not gonna peel garlic any more.
your mom wants me to..
stop peeling garlic
and concentrate on my study.
okay?
ya!
shut up and sleep.
okay, Jug-eun.
sleep tight, Jung-eun!
Jung-eun,
I forgot to tell you this.
I got the highest score from a test!
oh,
maybe it's not a big thing, but..
I wanna let you know about it,
that's all.
oh..
what am I gonna eat?
I can't find anything good.
you can't?
then you can peel garlic
or eat your tent.
hello?
chief!
you remember the plant you gave to me?
yes,
you promised to find a name of it.
what's its name?
I don't know it yet.
sorry.
by the way,
are you doing anything this afternoon?
okay, see you there.
ya,
you hate this cat so much.
no, I don't~
I don't get why cat hates cat.
what?
no, nothing.
ya,
what does your chief think you are?
a toy for him?
he's always calling you up when he's get bored.
what?
he shouldn't do that.
people will misunderstand it.
don't worry.
I can handle it.
yeah, I know you can handle it, but..
I mean,
I hope you not to have dinner with him..
and not to get on his car..etc.
in short, you better not see him privately!
and he did that to him, right?
uh?
what do you mean?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
oh, you were drunk at that time?
that's why he's a playboy!
making you drunk and do that to you?
oh, what a..
anyway, don't spend time with him anymore.
understand?
ya,
you understand what I'm saying?
have your breakfast.
it's gonna rain in the afternoon.
collect the laundry when it rains.
I'm going out!
I don't care about
whom you're gonna see!
ya!
I'm not gonna collect 'em!
come back before 6!
don't drink with him again!
Jung-eun, come home early..
Jung-eun..
how about some wine?
no, thanks.
a cup of coffee for me.
I'll take wine.
you said you've got something to tell me.
what is it?
oh, you don't have to find
the name of the plant you gave to me.
I named it.
'my Jung-eun'
I'm sorry?
I named it 'my Jung-eun'.
it's very country-style..
just like you.
chief,
I gotta tell you something.
I think I gotta give it back to you.
'cause the cat at my home
hates this cat so much.
I don't think I can keep it.
so I'm giving it back to you.
no matter how many rough times
it gives to me,
the cat at my home is
the most important one to me.
I don't think I can raise..
another cat.
I'm sorry to tell you this.
Jung-eun, Jung-eun!
Jung-eun!
were you waiting for me?
you can give a call!
I told you to come back before 6.
your umbrella.
thanks.
ya!
it's broken!
but yours is good one!
no, yours is good one too!
okay, let me have yours.
let's use it together.
Kyung-min,
Kyung-min Lee!
oh, Hye-ryun!
Hye-ryun,
you can't even hear me calling you?
oh, I lost myself in the book..
I heard that you got the highest score
from the test.
congratulations!
oh, it's just a trial test.
you can buy me a drink.
good, I'll buy you a drink.
how about tonight?
well, today is..
why?
you've got an appointment?
sort of.
my granma told me to come home early tonight.
that's alright.
how about tomorrow, then?
tomorrow's okay.
I'll buy you decent dinner!
good, see you tomorrow.
see ya.
Kyung-min,
I'll drive you home.
drive me home?
let's go.
Hye-ryun,
I gotta finish this book..
get up,
I'll take you home.
oh, I'm..
okay.
I guess your granma's very happy
with you back home.
yes, she is.
she wants to thank you
'cause you took me back to home.
you wanna get in and see her?
sounds good.
okay, let's get inside.
Hye-ryun!
oh I forgot
we're having some guests tonight.
my granma's very busy now.
you can see her next time.
thank you for driving me home, bye!
you're weird today.
weird?
never mind.
bye.
bye, Hye-ryun!
take care!
Jung-eun!
you said you're almost home.
how come it took so long?
the traffic jam was so tough!
oh..the bus wasn't moving!
traffic jam at dinner time is tough.
this chige(=stew) got little bit thick.
it's alright for me.
what happened to your right hand?
I've been studying
holding a pencil all day loooong.
I can't even hold a spoon now.
my right hand is aching!
don't lie to me.
it's true!
from 9 a.m., I've been holding a pencil like this..
ouch..
I don't think I can hold my spoon.
you feed me, ah~
I'm hungry. feed me.
I can't use my right hand.
you're so funny.
I'm hungry.
ah~~
I want ham first.
with ketchup!
Hye-ryun..
why did you come here again?
you guys are so funny, huh?
Hye-ryun, my hand is aching..
Hye-ryun!
where are you going?
- wait up,
- get off me!
let me explain.
I don't wanna hear from you!
I came here just to have dinner with her,
because she said she's bored home alone..
Kyung-min Lee,
uh?
game is over with you!
Hye-ryun,
you're misunderstanding something!
don't ever call me again.
it's all over!
hello..hello?
Hye-ryun!
what am I supposed to do?
Hye-ryun,
let me explain the situation,
( you misunderstood something. )
no, I don't wanna hear you
lying to me again.
Hye-ryun, I'm not lying to you.
I can't believe you any more.
so, if you wanna recover our relationship,
tell Jung-eun to come to me and explain the situation.
uh?
nothing more to say to you.
I'm not very patient, so..
it's up to you now.
( Kyung-min, )
( hello, )
( hello? )
one more bottle of soju here!
Kyung-min!
you're drunk?
yeah, I'm drunk.
let's go home.
sit down.
where have you been?
I've been to Hye-ryun's home..
oh yeah?
what did she say to you?
uh?
I don't know...
she doesn't wanna talk to me.
see?
she's very sharp tempered.
I told you before.
no..
what?
Jung-eun..
can you do just one favor for me?
what kind of favor?
can you go to see Hye-ryun and..
tell her that we're just friends..
and I like noboby but Hye-ryun..
can't you do that for me?
what did you just say?
are you insane?
why do I have to tell
that sort of things to Hye-ryun?
oh..
but you're my friend, aren't you?
last time,
I stamped on the memorandum for you
as a friend..
can't you return the favor?
what?
you think that makes sense?
you said you like me..
can't you do that for me?
I feel like..
I could just die..without Hye-ryun..
I'm sorry, Jung-eun...
die! you die!
you're so bad, you die!
you better die!
you're so bad!
you die..
( when you're holding me tight.. )
( I can hear.. )
( I can hear you breathing.. )
( it feels so good.. )
( I could almost cry.. )
( a memorandum )
( I, Kyung-min Lee, )
( will marry Jung-eun Nam )
( after I passed the bar exam. )
( you're the biggest gift.. )
( from the sky to me.. )
Jung-eun,
give me some water..
Jung-eun!
Jung-eun..
where is she?
where has she gone to?
why did you call me up?
you know why, don't you?
I know why?
I don't think so.
I have no idea.
I'll tell you what you wanna hear from me.
Kyung-min & me are just friends.
and he likes..
nobody but you.
nobody can replace you.
nobody compares to you..
are you satisfied now?
by the way,
why are you keeping him at your place?
that's..
that's because I borrowed some money from him.
so he's staying at my place
until I pay the money back to him.
that's all.
is that all?
yeah, that's all.
you..
you slept with him, right?
say what?
you really did?
no, I didn't.
you didn't?
no.
getting a guy
by sleeping with him..
that's the worst thing a girl can do.
it's very sad
there's still a girl like you.
ya!
what?
you wanna hit me on my face again?
you already forgot why you came here?
I will forgive Kyung-min this time.
what a sad story you're making..
I didn't know that
you like Kyung-min this much.
no. not any more.
I gave him up.
he's so hopeless.
you & Kyung-min..
both are hopeless jerks like garbage.
I gotta go.
I'm busy.
bye.
Kyung-min!
Hye-ryun!
Hye-ryun..
sorry for yesterday's thing..
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I didn't have chance
to say goodbye to Jung-eun, so..
I came to her place
to say goodbye and..
she made dinner for me..
it's alright.
I met Jung-eun and she cleared my misunderstanding.
Jung-eun..
she came here?
she explained the situation to me.
I think I misunderstood something.
she seems to like you so much.
you asked her to see me, right?
oh, she just did what you want her to do.
I felt sorry for her..
I think she'd better find another guy
who fits her status.
now she learned that you don't like her.
that's actually good for her.
she can find another guy now.
oh, she's just a stupid idiot!
( I'm sorry.. )
( don't cry.. )
( now I'm back here for you.. )
( now I know that.. )
( I can't be happy.. )
( without you.. )
( when you're holding me tight.. )
( I can hear.. )
( I can hear you breathing.. )
( it feels so good.. )
( I could almost cry.. )
( now I'm back here for you.. )
( I can see your tears here.. )
( it's breaking my heart.. )
hi,
( but now it's okay.. )
( you're the biggest gift.. )
( from the sky to me.. )
I like you..
( now I'm back here for you.. )
( I can see your tears here.. )
( it's breaking my heart.. )
( but now it's okay.. )
( you're the biggest gift.. )
( from  the sky to me.. )
Jung-eun..
you idiot..
how could..
how could you really do that?
Jung-eun..
I like you..
I think it's very hard..
to like somebody.
it's very difficult for me..
nobody taught me
what is love & what it's like to like someone..
same for you, right?
it's the fault of the education system!
what is calculus,
what is 'hello' & 'hi'..
those are not very important, you know.
what's important is..
'what is love?'
and 'what's the difference between love & like'.
they should teach it,
don't you think so?
Jung-eun..
I'm..
Kyung-min,
let's put an end to it.
let's get apart.
Jung-eun,
yesterday's thing was..
Kyung-min,
it's not because I got mad at you..
and I'm not saying this to threaten you..
I'm serious now..
please get out of my place..
Jung-eun..
can you imagine..
how I felt when I saw Hye-ryun?
I did the last thing I can do.
so..
you think about it, and..
tell me when you're gonna get out of my place..
Jung-eun : Da-bin Jung
Kyung-min : Rae-won Kim
Hye-ryun : Jung-yoon Choi
Dong-june : Hyun-woo Lee
Copyright 2003 MBC production, Korea
English subtitles by TOTUTA
jwc93@hanmail.net
http://atticcat.wo.to