Hello, gentlemen.
I have come to take your lives.
PIERROT LE FOU
Hello, boy.
Your partner sure is unlucky, Jet.
Well, he wasn’t all that
lucky to begin with…
This case is especially bad.
It would be better to not get
yourselves involved in this one.
I don’t care, just answer me. Now.
I’m telling you this
for your own sake, and…
…if you get too involved in this,
I’m gonna get in trouble, too.
You know, Bob…
You’re the only person
I can rely on right now.
I’ll make sure it won’t
be bad for you. So…
Don’t you say that every time?
Really… you always have been a guy
that likes to get into trouble…
All right, this is only a rumor, but…
Have you heard of
the name “Mad Pierrot”?
There he is… the rumored mummy.
So, I heard you got beaten
up by some weird guy?
I recall you were sleeping
like this once before.
You really haven’t shown
any improvement…
Oh well, it doesn’t have
anything to do with me.
Don’t you end up in situations
like that because you never behave?
Well, I have nothing to do with it.
So, since I have nothing to
do with it, if you’ll excuse me…
Take care.
The victim was a high-ranking
guy from the ISSP.
He was the seventh victim.
What did you say?
Can’t blame ya. This is top-secret.
Apparently those higher-ups don’t
want the world to find out about this.
Why?
Your partner is in deep trouble.
The guy is a perfect killing machine.
They say that nobody who has seen
his face has made it out alive…
Even those lucky enough to escape’ll be
tracked down to the ends of the world…
…and they always wind up dead.
They say he appears with a smile,
and he leaves with a smile…
Yeah, he is the mysterious
assassin known as Mad Pierrot…
Tongpu.
Faye-Faye!
Puff, puff! Faye-Faye!
Puff, puff! Faye-Faye…
Hey you, can you stop saying
my name twice like that?
Faye-Faye, a weird mail came, came.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
…and I woulda been done if
I had a little more time…
I can’t read it!
“Hello, boy. I’ll invite
you to a wonderful party…”
Wait, this is…
Listen, keep the fact that this
mail came a secret from Spike.
Secret?
Why?
Why secret?
If we don’t, that idiot…
…will run out to meet him?
It’s a secret, secret mail!
Space Land?
Pretty considerate of him
to hold the party there.
You’re gonna go like that?
Well, it would be perfect
if it was a masquerade.
Maybe this one really
will be the end of me…
Just kidding!
Would you come rescue
me if I said that?
Idiot.
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Hey…
Oh, it’s you, Ed. Where’s Spike?
He went somewhere.
What?
Not that this is anything new…
That idiot…
Idiot, idiot?
Ed, I have a favor to ask.
What, what?
Hello!
Welcome!
Yo…
Let’s party!
You can’t enter here!
It’s dangerous in here!
Let’s play outside!
Shut up!
It’s dangerous in here!
Let’s play outside!
Hi!
All right, Ed…
First, enter the ISSP’s main
computer, and look for section 13.
Aye, aye!
That’s the section that doesn’t
exist to the general public.
It’s a pretty tall order…
Can you do it?
Yup!
Hello!
Found it!
After you open it, find the
file with the code name “Tongpu.”
Yup!
Peek-a…
…boo!
ISSP Assassination Ability,
Improvement Experiment.
Experiment sample chart number 46.
Code name: Tongpu.
Confirmed a strong regression
of the mind during…
…the experiment.
Experiment was canceled.
Sample to be permanently kept
in a quarantine facility,
In the beginning, he escaped
from the facilities to seek revenge…
…but now he seems to be enjoying
the actual act of killing.
His mind must be
continuing to regress.
So, he’s like a child with
superhuman fighting abilities.
Really…
There is nothing as pure
and cruel as children.
It’s show time!
That was unnecessary!
Hello, hello…
Hello! Hello!
Hello…
T-That hurts!
It hurts!
It hurts!!
Hurts…
Mommy, it hurts!
Mommy!!
It hurts… Mommy!
Spike! All right,
we figured out what he is! He’s…
No. I don’t need it anymore…
It all ended just now…
Aishiteta to nageku niwa…
Too much time has passed by…
…amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
…to lament that we were deeply in love.
Mada kokoro no hokorobi wo…
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart…
…iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
…cannot heal all the tears in it.
Kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
Honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Doro no kawa ni tsukatta…
Sitting in muddy water…
…jinsei mo waruku wa nai…
…isn’t such a bad life…
…ichido kiri de owaru nara…
…if it ends after the first time…
COMING EPISODE
I knew there was something
fishy going on lately.
So, that’s what it was!
What are you guys talking about?
You really can’t judge
people by their looks…
Honestly disgusting.
Hey, hey, what are you
guys talking about?
I never thought it would
be a teenage girl…
It makes me despise him.
Who are you talking about?
Next episode: “Boogie Woogie Feng Shui”.
I didn’t do anything!
BOOGIE WOOGIE
FENG SHUI