Hmm.
[inhales sharply]
I can see the blade now.
Steel glistening wet
as it pulls across the flesh.
Knowing that with
a simple flick of the wrist...
veins will open.
Blood will flow. [shudders]
[exhales heavily]
It's ecstasy.
Let me get this straight, you let a woman
shave your balls with a straight razor.
- I wasn't gonna let a man do it.
- It wasn't my point but...
You have to use a straight razor.
Electrics are like bloody chainsaws.
Who shaves you?
This'll come as a shock to you,
but most people don't like
sharp blades near their dicks.
Tell me you trim, at least.
- [Spike] Please stop.
- Oh, you savage.
[Spike laughs]
I prefer a more natural situation.
That's just uncivilized.
At the very least, you could braid it.
- [chuckling] Braid it!
- Although they're not long enough.
- [snickers]
- [laughs]
[man] Look, just tell him to wait.
Judge Bradley agreed to sign the warrants.
Yeah, it's actually happening.
We're taking down The Syndicate.
Can you... [choking]
[woman over phone] Lee, are you okay?
[continues choking]
[woman] Answer me. Are you...
[coughing]
What the hell?
[sighs]
Look at me.
Look at me!
How does it feel?
[Spike] Pretty sure
it doesn't feel like ecstasy.
Hard to tell, frankly.
Look at this mess.
This is why I was using a garrote.
Well, you looked like you were struggling.
Besides, I, I felt inspired.
[Spike] Clean up the blood.
Find something to...
Why should I clean up? I did all the work.
Are you kidding me?
I am not cleaning up any blood.
You are doing all...
It'll only be a minute, sweetie.
I just left some...
- [gasps]
- [Spike] Don't.
Come back.
[shuddering]
What's your name?
- [shakily] Brenda.
- [Spike] Brenda.
- You didn't see anything here.
- [Brenda shudders]
[Spike] Nod if you understand me.
Run!
What is the matter with you?
She could ID us.
No kids. That's the code.
- You're such a candy apple, Fearless.
- [sighs]
[Vicious] Mercy is for the weak.
[grunts softly]
[theme music playing]
- [jazz music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[women laughing]
[Stax] You take care of our little problem
at the courthouse?
Can you believe it?
Turns out the judge never got
the paperwork from the DA.
You'd think something that important
you'd follow through.
- It's just lazy.
- [Vicious] Mm.
[Stax] Good.
So...
Come on, you stupid piece of...
Fucking synth beef.
I mean, seriously, how hard would it be
to breed a couple of cows?
Everything is so goddamn phony these days.
I've got another job for you two.
If you want us to breed cows,
it's gonna take some time, sir.
Sit down, wise guys.
You're making people nervous.
[grunts]
So, the Elders are looking
to negotiate a deal
- with the Neptune cartel.
- Those animals?
For what?
For the fact that it rains diamonds
on Neptune, you believe that shit?
The Syndicate wants a piece
in exchange for distribution.
And you two are gonna
broker the deal with their man Ka-Ching.
Us?
Well, him, really.
Isn't that more your job?
Damn straight it's my job.
Then again, it's also my job
to groom the likes of you.
Brokering a deal of this magnitude
is what Capos do.
And the sooner you learn how,
the sooner I get to pass the torch.
Live out the rest of my days
on a fucking boat somewhere.
Eating what I can only hope
is a real goddamn steak as God intended.
[Spike chuckles]
So, don't fuck this up.
Your future and mine hinge on it.
Here's what you do...
You open at 40%,
you settle...
at 25.
I'll get the 40.
Mademoiselle.
[waitress] Mm-hmm?
A Kudo for my friend here, I'll have...
What are you doing? Excuse us.
This is a Capo's table.
You wanna drink, drink at your own table.
You stay.
[Spike sighs]
Unbe-fucking-lievable.
My life's not hard enough,
I've gotta bring up an Elder's kid.
- Not everyone's a people person...
- Oh, please.
I know your type,
but don't pretend you didn't see it.
There's something rotten in him.
He's all right.
[Stax] That's only
'cause you clean up after him.
This Neptune thing is a ripe deal.
That's why they want you on it too,
to make sure,
to make dead bang sure he doesn't blow it.
You hear me?
Yes, sir.
Else it's all our heads.
I'll take care of him.
[playing upbeat jazz music]
Hey. Serpiente and a Kudo. Onegaishimasu.
Thirsty night?
I'm working up the courage
to ask you to dance again.
I keep telling you
you're too skinny for me.
- Too skinny? That hurts.
- [Ana chuckles]
[Spike] Ouch.
Things looked pretty serious with Stax.
- Yeah, it's all good.
- Uh-huh.
Still won't let you
drink with him, will he?
Everybody knows
the cool kids sit in the back anyway.
[laughs]
- Who's on the tray tonight?
- Kiki.
Kiki?
God knows why,
but all the girls fight over your table.
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
- [Ana chuckles]
Well, I only have eyes for you.
- Ah...
- Listen, you, me, dancefloor, tonight.
No more lame excuses.
- Lame?
- [Spike] Always.
Please.
Wait, what was my excuse last night?
- Last night? I was too young.
- [Ana] Mmm.
Night before that, I wasn't rich enough.
Well, what can I say hotshot?
I like 'em old, rich and fat.
- [laughs] Oh, I'll start eating then.
- [laughing]
- Gotta run. Have fun.
- [Spike] All right.
Oh, it's okay.
You're gonna be okay now that you...
How is she?
- She'll be...
- [vomiting]
- She's next up.
- [Ana] Shit.
[woman vomiting]
- Seems to me you better get ready.
- Love that.
What?
- No.
- Yes.
- Oh, I can't...
- [Gren] You can.
No, no, seriously, I can't.
- Get her ready.
- [Gren] Mm-hmm.
[Julia] Ana, please.
Ana, you can't be serious.
- You're all smiles.
- [sighs]
I'm finally getting the respect I deserve.
It's about time.
The Syndicate is gonna be mine one day.
You know that, right?
I do. And I'm really happy for you.
For me? No, no, no.
Where I go, you go.
You'll be right there by my side.
The two of us together.
- Here's to us, brother.
- Brother.
[audience applauding]
[Gren speaks Spanish]
Shōnen, shōjo,
and all you dirty, dirty folks in between.
We have a unique treat
for you all tonight.
[whispers] A virgin.
[people cheering]
Innocent and demure, anointed and oiled.
And tonight she will submit herself to
the volcano of your approval and pleasure.
- [breathes deeply]
- She's one of my favorite people,
homegrown right here in Ana's,
so be nice to her
or there will be spankings.
[laughter]
Willkommen Julia.
[cheering and applause]
[exhales]
[sultry jazz music playing]
♪ Swath me ♪
♪ In honey ♪
♪ Wrap me ♪
♪ In stars ♪
♪ This world has teeth, my love ♪
♪ And I bear the scars ♪
♪ Wrap me ♪
♪ In honey, dear ♪
♪ Bathe me in stars ♪
♪ This world has teeth, love ♪
♪ But with you ♪
♪ I'm on Mars ♪
♪ This world has teeth ♪
♪ My love, my love, my love ♪
♪ But with you ♪
♪ I'm on Mars ♪
Some voice.
Some woman.
[applause and cheering]
[jazz music playing in background]
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
You were magnificent.
- Oh. I can't believe it, Ana. That was...
- It was perfect.
[chuckles]
Oh, you didn't have to.
I didn't.
An admirer sent it back.
Really?
Hmm. I brought it
despite my better judgment.
- Handsome?
- [Ana] Syndicate.
- And you know my feelings on them.
- [Julia] Mm-hmm.
They're like bears, fun to look at,
but don't roll down the windows.
Mm-hmm. [chuckles]
Enjoy the glow.
Just be careful with this.
[sighs]
[music continues]
- [Julia] This is quite the picnic.
- [birds chirping]
[Vicious] Well, I'm not
a blanket-on-the-ground kind of guy.
I may not be the first man
you ever went out with,
or kissed,
or loved...
But I want to be the last one.
[chuckles softly]
You speak Russian?
I learned a little,
knowing it was your native tongue.
[racy music playing]
[dings]
Wait.
- [Vicious clears throat]
- So, it's serious.
It's evolving.
Evolving? A dozen dates
and more on the horizon, that's serious.
Fine. I stipulate to serious.
And to think she's seen
parts of the real you
and she's eager for more.
That's mind-boggling.
[Vicious] We're going out later,
you should join.
Uh... [chuckling] Why would I do that?
She finds you funny somehow.
You talk about me on dates?
- During sex, actually.
- [laughs] Of course.
[Stax] Come.
Neptune Cartel's papers
just kicked up at the Martian Gate.
It's time to deal.
They do have rules of negotiation though.
[Vicious] Which are?
No iron.
[Vicious] Are you joking?
Not even.
Take the team for backup,
but you two go in naked.
- That's the plan.
- [Vicious exhales]
That's great.
We were born nudists.
[ominous music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Spike] He said no iron.
We don't answer to Stax.
I do.
You worry too much.
You don't worry enough.
Hang on to this.
It's absolutely stunning.
I know, right?
He gave it to me on Saturday.
Julia. I am so sorry. I just heard.
- Heard what?
- Ana.
She fired you.
What? Where is she?
She's backstage.
Gren just told me I was fired.
You know, there is one thing
I cannot abide by.
Ana, is this about my seeing...
People disobeying my rules.
Congratulations.
- [gasps]
- [Ana chuckles]
Wait, what? I thought you really fired me.
She did when I pointed out
that you were double-dipping.
No more collecting the check
for doing hair and makeup.
As of today, you only collect
as our new headliner.
[gasps]
[all cheering]
[chuckles softly] Oh, wow.
- You tried to cut off his fucking hand?
- [laughing]
That inbred animal insulted me,
insulted The Syndicate.
Did you think
this was just about diamonds?
You did, didn't you?
This was about The Syndicate
getting a foothold in the outer planets.
- We can fix this, sir.
- I haven't even started with you!
You're lug nuts!
The both of you are fucking lug nuts!
The fix will come down from the Elders.
You two will do nothing,
you will sit on your fucking hands
and wait until they tell me what to do,
then I will tell you what to do
and you will goddamn do it!
[Vicious sighs]
To hell with Stax.
To hell with all of them.
The Elders will see.
They'll say I've done the right thing.
We need to put the fear
into those Neptune savages.
Whatever happens, happens.
[Vicious] For you, maybe.
For me, there are...
expectations.
Fucking Ka-Ching!
[Julia] Hey! I made it.
Where were you?
Ah, there was a ship jam at the gate.
Took forever to clear.
Everything okay?
Yeah, just tough day at the office.
- This place is amazing, by the way.
- [Vicious scoffs]
Sarcasm doesn't suit you.
[Spike] Hey, I was being serious.
Everybody loves a dive bar.
How you doing tonight?
- Excellent, thank you.
- [Spike] Yeah.
[sighs]
Ana made me a headliner.
[Julia chuckles]
Well, celebrations are in order. Cheers!
- Cheers. Thank you.
- [Spike] Yeah
Congratulations.
- [upbeat music playing]
- [people cheering]
[Julia] I love the Jupiter jig.
Hey. Come on, dance with me.
I don't think so.
Dance with your girl. It'll cheer you up.
You go, if you like this place so much.
[Spike] I love places like this
for getting shit-faced.
Which I prefer doing over dancing.
All right, I guess it's on you.
[chuckling] It's on me?
[chuckles]
All right.
Just to be clear, I'm no dancer.
You have feet, you can dance.
I do have feet. [chuckles]
- All right.
- Hey.
Is he okay?
I've never seen him so intense.
Him? Oh, I've seen him intense,
that's not intense.
That's... That's almost playful.
[chuckles]
So, how did you two end up partners?
We met when we were kids.
He saved me.
He convinced his father to take me in,
build a life for me.
We became brothers that day.
I grew up on the streets, no family,
no prospects, no chance for survival. So...
I'm sorry.
Don't be. Don't be.
Never thought there was any use
in denying the past.
- You sure about this?
- Yeah. It's easy. Come on.
Okay.
- What do I do?
- Keep your eyes on me.
- Excuse me, I'm sorry.
- [laughing]
[Spike] Switch side.
Tricky.
[Julia chuckles]
[Spike] Don't say I didn't warn you.
Yep. Switching sides again.
Getting the hang of it.
- [Julia] Hey!
- [Spike] Hey!
- Ooh!
- Oh.
[camera flashes]
[camera whirring]
[photographer] Huh. Fun memories.
[Julia clears throat]
- Wanna get out of here? Yeah.
- Yeah.
I know a nightclub in Tharsis
where he'll be much happier.
You're a good friend.
[Spike and Julia laughing]
[Julia] And then what happened?
I go to shake the guy's hand
and that's when I see he's got no arms.
- No.
- [Spike] I don't want to be rude.
My hands are already out.
So I shook his head.
- No, you didn't.
- [Spike] I did.
- [Vicious] He did, that he did.
- Oh, my God! What did he do?
He kicked the shit out of me.
- You let him kick the shit out of you.
- [laughing]
Of course I let him kick
the shit out of me.
It was the least I could do!
The guy had no arms!
Son of a bitch.
- What?
- [indistinct chatter]
- What is it?
- It's Ka-Ching. That Neptune scum.
Vicious, wait.
- Vicious, Stop!
- Vicious, what are you doing? Stop!
- Vicious, stop! Stop!
- [Julia] Vicious, stop!
[Julia gasps]
Don't. Vicious!
- [Vicious] You wanna fuck with me?
- [Ka-Ching screams]
[sobbing]
You wanna fuck with The Syndicate?
[Spike] Stop! You're gonna kill him.
[Vicious grunts]
[Spike] Vicious, stop.
[crying]
Take her home. I'll deal with him.
[breathing heavily]
- [Vicious grunts]
- [crying]
[car engine rumbling]
[sighs]
[exhales]
My hands.
They're shaking.
I can't make it stop.
[breathing heavily]
[slow jazz music playing]
[Ka-Ching groans]
[coughs]
Look at me.
You're safe now.
You're safe with me.
[Julia] I know.
[Ka-Ching] Please, no! Please!
[both grunting]
[Ka-Ching panting]
[grunting]
[sobbing]
Yes.
[music tempo increases]
[music tempo decreases]
[music fades]
[chuckles]
What?
All my life...
I've tried not to feel anything,
to not care about anything...
'cause if I did,
I'd have something to lose.
Something to be afraid of.
And right now...
all I'm afraid of is losing you.
Is this a dream?
[cell phone vibrating]
Is that him?
Worse.
Were you with him?
What are you talking about?
I call you at 3:00 in the morning
and you're gonna fuck with me?
Were you with your partner
when he killed Ka-Ching?
It wasn't him. It was me. We ran...
Spare me. He did it in the goddam street!
As if nobody was gonna see.
I know you think you owe him.
But a sane person would wonder,
"How long are you gonna pay that debt?"
I can fix it, sir. You just give me 24...
No. No, no, no, it's over!
Vicious crossed the line.
There are consequences!
The Neptune cartel wants him dead.
- And if we don't comply...
- It's gonna be war.
It's worse, it's last man standing.
Everybody fucking knows...
if there are survivors...
the war never ends.
His father, he's not gonna allow it.
You'd think.
Actually,
Caliban sanctioned it.
And he wants you to do it.
- What?
- He wants you to do it.
No, I won't.
[Stax] Whatever. You don't want to?
Somebody else will.
He figured at least
you'd make it quick.
All my life...
whatever trouble I got myself into...
if I couldn't buy my way out,
you'd talk us out.
If I failed my father's name...
[sighs]
My fucking father.
You know, he made me watch
the night my mother jumped.
Nine years old.
I watched as she contemplated
her mortality while standing on the roof.
I could barely comprehend it.
My father, my fucking...
father...
didn't move a muscle to help her.
He just kept whispering in my ear...
how weak she was.
Over and over.
And then... [laughs]
when I cried...
as I saw her step off that ledge... [laughs]
he started telling me
how weak I was for shedding a tear.
He's right.
He's always been right.
Like her...
I am weak.
Killing that animal...
It was weakness.
[sighs]
You shouldn't be here.
Any second they'll be coming for me.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
[somber music playing]
[lighter clicking]
[laughter]
[creaks]
- [man 1] Hey!
- [gunshot]
- [man 2] What the fuck?
- [man 3 screaming]
- [gunshots]
[man 4] What the fuck?
[man 5] Don't shoot me, please!
[men screaming]
- [Spike grunts]
- [man 2] Find the motherfucker!
[grunts]
[yelps]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[yells]
- [choking]
- [man 6 yells]
[man 2] Get in there!
[screams]
[man 7 screams]
[music playing]
- [grunts]
- [body thuds]
[girl shudders]
You didn't see anything here.
This never happened, do you understand me?
Run.
Run!
[body thuds]
[ominous music playing]
[Spike] I can't keep doing this.
This life.
This madness.
I don't want this to be who I am anymore.
I'm leaving.
Tonight.
Run away with me.
We, we can't.
Yes, we can.
- We can.
- No.
We can go someplace
where we can just be us.
He'll never stop looking for us.
I'll make sure he never finds us.
I promise you.
- Fearless...
- [Spike] Julia...
I love you.
I have since the moment I saw you.
Yes. [sniffles]
Yes.
[sniffles]
Midnight.
Tonight. Under the bridge.
I'll be there.
I need your help.
I need new papers, a new name.
New everything.
You know you can't run.
- Nobody can outrun The Syndicate.
- I need papers for Julia, too.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, don't do this!
Not with her.
Her chances with me
are better than with Vicious.
You know that.
Promise me you will keep her safe.
You have my word.
I wish I could say I was happy for you,
but I'm not.
[Spike] Mmm.
Beautiful.
May I?
Where did you get these?
You think you're the only ones
that can fall in love?
Gren'll make good on the papers.
Thank you.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[snoring]
[Caliban] Quite the celebration
you've had.
[groaning]
[inhales]
Father.
I should've come to you. I apologize.
Apologize?
No.
I've come to congratulate you.
What you and Fearless did...
Who thought it possible?
Two men against an entire cartel.
I may have underestimated you, boy.
I'm proud of you.
Well, they disrespected The Syndicate.
They disrespected you,
I couldn't let that...
- That's enough!
- [grunts]
[Caliban] Worthless!
And worse, you are a fucking liar!
You're an embarrassment.
- A meaningless slug!
- [Vicious groaning]
Whose only achievements
come from the doings of others.
Oh, how I dreamt that one day you would
prove yourself to be man enough.
But alas.
I should've ended you long ago.
But here you still are by some miracle.
- Fearless...
- Yes, Fearless.
Fearless is a wild card in the deck.
I'd anticipated his loyalty
to be singular to The Syndicate,
but you believed it was to you!
And the irony for both of us
was that he was only ever
loyal to himself.
While you were neck-deep in the bottle,
your brother was stepping out
with your whore!
- He wouldn't.
- He did.
And papers were processed.
They're not just running around on you,
they're running away from you.
[Caliban grunts]
Where are they?
[exhales]
[Caliban sighs]
You want to be a capo?
Capos don't ask questions.
They find answers.
[door closes]
[grunting]
Hello, Ana.
What do you want?
Where is Fearless taking her?
I don't know what you're talk...
How would you like
these next few moments to go?
Piss off, cunt.
[exhales]
Everyone thinks they're so strong.
Until they're not.
- [grunts]
- [Ana screaming]
[Vicious] Where is he?
Vicious wants me
to bring you to his penthouse.
What?
- No, I-I'm...
- The streets are dangerous tonight
and he wants to keep you safe.
So, please just leave that here
and come with me.
- [ship horn blowing in distance]
- [bell tolling]
[footsteps approaching]
[ominous music playing]
Well, she's not coming.
Not tonight.
Not ever.
She chose me.
Think you're fast enough?
[groans]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[rock music playing]