"I'll become the ensign
to bring them all together," eh?
You really think that's possible
inside this giant trash beast?
It's easier than you'd think
to make a big production.
You just need to put a lot of power into it.
You think that power of yours
can get you out of here alone?
Hey, now.
Didn't I say it?
We're all in this together!
He... Did he figure out
the direction his allies are in?
Yeah, he did!
Do the Cleaners have something
that tells them the position of their allies?
Hell no!
But his hunches usually just turn out right!
Hunches?!
Nailed it.
You broke through the body to come here?
I'm impressed that you
ascertained our location.
But it's just one more person.
Thanks for carving me a path here, Enjin!
I was totally lost, y'know?
Hey, looks like you're—
In awful shape! Zanka, are you even alive?!
Guita! Is that where you were?
I hit my head.
Are you okay?
Just gonna sleep.
Th-There?!
Hey, Zanka?!
Looks like my whole team's still alive, Zodyl.
I'm sick of your rambling experiment shit.
The trash beast's core is right here.
And the Cleaners are over there.
You get it? Your experiment's over.
That's right, Rudo.
We'll observe what happens
when it crosses the border
and have our conclusion soon.
There.
Let's set you down here.
Hey, you didn't kill...
No killing!
No killing, no way!
The angle's changing?
At last.
It did take some time.
Now, let us begin.
Death, or the Sphere—
it's a race against time to the border.
Episode 21
TIME ATTACK
You sure like to run your mouth,
but we both know...
we just have to stop this trash beast, right?
If it's powered by a vital instrument,
it's no different than that trash beast
I saw them take out during my training!
Which means...
If we just destroy the vital instrument
at the core before we get there...
We can consider it cleaned!
It's like a gun!
Hang on, that means...
We're inside a trash beast?
Neither the experiment or my training
is over yet.
Hey there!
I'm actually a Raider-in-training...
A newbie.
Bundus?!
Y-You're a newbie?
Well, I should have had
a little more urgency.
I'd better show off
what I can really do now.
Which means...
I'll crush you all with all I've got!
You split into two groups?
Then I'll use two hands.
Split into four groups?
Four hands, then.
If you add one more in...
Five hands.
My Hands are prosthetic arms that became
part of me when I reached certain ages.
Can you tell?
They're all high quality.
Can you get through them
before we cross the border?
And I've got one more hand to spare.
The other newbie is hard at work.
What will you do?
Out of the fight already?
Like hell.
I won't let it end like this!
The core.
I just need to destroy that core.
That's all I need to do, and yet...
I can't reach it!
Get out of the way!
Breaking... through!
For you, I'll use this hand!
Third hand—from when I turned twenty.
A time when I was starting to stretch my wings.
I'll cut through it, then!
You'll understand this someday, too...
When you get older,
you become more conservative.
Sixth hand—from when I turned forty.
Second hand—from when I turned eighteen.
When I failed to realize my own immaturity
and kept a sharp edge on my personality.
Fifth hand—from when I turned thirty-five.
An age when I felt adrift and unfocused.
So he's got multiple vital instruments?
Some newbie!
Me and Dear aside, he instantly grasped
the essence of the others' vital instruments
and doled out the hands
that could best deal with them!
He's a seasoned veteran!
If only we had Guita's power at our disposal,
we could probably get out of this, but...
Bundus seems acceptable.
A well-worn instrument,
of sufficient quality to move
as a part of his body.
But users of multiple
vital instruments are rare,
and if you mistake him for one,
you'll never break through.
I've recovered Jabber.
He says he went all-out like you wanted,
so he hopes you'll play with him.
It seems he still needs more correction.
Well then...
I think it's about time we got out of here.
Dammit!
He split us up really cleverly.
Crap!
This should be close enough.
Huh? What's that?
Hey! Welcome back.
Crap... This is really bad!
I can't break past this guy!
I'm truly grateful.
You gave me the perfect chance
to show off my talents.
How far up has the trash beast gotten now?
How long until we cross the border?
If you cross the border, you die...
But how do you die?
Not even Enjin and the others can get past him.
Isn't there anything I can do?!
No...
You're wrong, Rudo.
Your 3R here... Regto gave them to you.
No, he passed them on to you!
And that's not all!
They're the treasure you've
taken care of all these years!
I've had them and cared for them
every bit as much as he has!
That means...
Rudo?
Stronger... I can get even stronger!
I can get stronger.
What's that, then?
Huh? It was a nail gun before, right?
Did he swap for another piece of trash?
Nah.
I think he's sticking with that one this time.
How do you know that?
Rudo's power lets him reuse
up to three pieces of trash
and broken things as weapons.
I don't think he realizes it, but the reason
he can make multiple weapons
is because he's splitting the power
of his gloves, 3R, between each one.
But if he focuses all
that power into one piece...
You kidding me?
But then he'll use all his power
in one shot and pass out again.
I doubt he's considering
what'll happen if he overworks himself.
Channeling all your power into it,
damn the consequences?
Inexperienced boy.
He's impulsive and reckless.
But right now, that's the biggest threat to me.
It's hard to stop an idiot
from doing what they want!
Just get out of the way already!
It's so powerful!
But still unrefined!
One more shot!
My... Hands...
So close!
He almost had it! A little more
to the left and he'd have hit it!
But he took the old man down!
Now let's hit the core!
It's not easy, is it?
Even if you can fix it,
seeing something you love lie
in shattered pieces before you...
Every single time I see it...
It hurts.
Rudo... come on.
You can't go projecting all your empathy
onto other people's things too.
Good work, Bundus.
Come join us.
Huh? I haven't stopped anyone, though.
You've given me an idea of your capabilities.
Besides...
It's just about time.
We're almost at the border?
I've confirmed the sensation
and endurance of the vehicle,
observed the power of
the new Raiders, offered correction,
confirmed the capabilities of the chokers,
and witnessed the power of another
entry in the Watchman Series.
There's no reason for us
to stay here any longer.
Up we go.
Really glad to hear it.
Hey. You...
Your vital instrument...
You care deeply about objects, don't you?
All of my prosthetic arms integrate
parts of the original prosthetic arm I used.
You can't help but have a special attachment
to the first one you ever got.
It's like the core of my vital instrument.
I said earlier, remember? I can fix it.
No, to hell with that!
You're just running away?!
Running away?
I'm doing as I planned.
The rest of you are the guinea pigs.
Why would we remain in the cage with you?
You're the ones who brought us here!
You don't get to have your way!
Then stop barking at me and
destroy the core, why don't you?
No, it's too late now.
You should have done it before
another enthusiastic newbie arrived.
Riyo...